Guide to the Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files 1922-2004 (bulk, 1923-1989) MS 3009-RG 21
New-York Historical Society
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: "Of Hemlines, Deadlines and Sales" (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Rates (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Service to Advertisers Kit (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: "Speaking of Pictures" (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: "Two Worlds" (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Uncle Ben's Converted Rice (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: "Roman Piazza" (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: "What's Life?" (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 3-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Ads: "How I Feel About Life" (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 6-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Attleboro City-Wide (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Building (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Circulation (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Fact Sheets, Editorial (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Filene's Department Store (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: General Electric (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Market Research and TV: Politz, Duplicating Study (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Medical School (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Merchandising for Project Program (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: "More than a Hurricane Hit Attleboro" (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Panorama City City-Wide (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Rates [empty] (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Savignac, "You Get ... out of Life" (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: "Something Big in Burlingame" (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: "Twenty Thousand Leagues under the Sea" (Offsite-box 3535, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 15-16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Ads: "How I Feel about Life" (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 4-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Circulation (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Food (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: "How Life Brings It Home" (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: "How Life Gets the Story" (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 9-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Rates (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3503, Folder 21)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Service to Advertisers Kit (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Wichita Parade of Homes (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Year-End Issue, "Christianity" (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 3-4)
  1 phonograph record (33 1/2 rpm); 7 in. Label on Side A: "Jet Scramble. Recorded for the General Electric Company by Emory Cook with the cooperation of the U.S. Air Force. GEN 114-A. Sound Story of a F-86D Sabre Jet Interceptor 'scramble.'" Label on Side B: "Sounds of Jet Aircraft. Band 1. Speed run, two F-86D's. Band 2. Two Jets landing. Band 3. Sabres approach hangar, cut engines. Band 4. Two F-86D's climb out overhead." Label on container: "Jet Scramble. Sounds of an Air Defense Command Mission. General Electric."
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: "A Child Reared in a Lonely Tower" (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Ads: "How I Feel about Life" (Offsite-box 3536, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3537, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3537, Folder 2-3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956-1957: Advance Mailing Program for Salesmen (AMPS) (Offsite-box 3537, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: "All About Eve" (Offsite-box 3537, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: "American Woman" (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Blockbuster Reprints (Offsite-box 3537, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Circulation (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 6-7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: "Great Moments from Life" (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: "Great Moments from Life" (Offsite-box 3537, Folder 8-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Haag Drugstores Promotion (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: "Photography of Bourke-White" (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: "Point of Sale" (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Rates (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Retail Representatives: Manual (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Retail Representatives: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 16-17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 18-19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3537, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Ads: "How I Feel about Life" (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Ads: "How People Respond to Life" (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Blockbusters (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Circulation (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Department Store Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Job Index (Offsite-box 3504, Folder 21)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Life Photographers: Their Careers and Favorite Pictures, Stanley Rayfield (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 9-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Market Research and TV: Consumer Expenditures Study (LSCE) #1 (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 1-2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Market Research and TV: "Point of Sale" (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: McCormack Place (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Merchandising Manual (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: "The Pace of Life" (Offsite-box 3538, Item 1-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Regional Editions (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 1)
  1 phonograph record (33 1/3 rpm); 12 in. On label: "Get in de Sell. Black Stef and his Kalypso Kings. 1-Convention Lament. 2-Man Smart, Life Salesman Smarter. 3-Get in de Sell." On container: "Get in de Sell... Black Stef and his Kalypso Kings. Point Clear, Alabama. May 1957."
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Service to Advertisers Kit (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Year-End Issue, "American's World" (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 12-15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Ads: "How I Feel about Life" (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3539, Folder 16-19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Blockbusters (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Circulation (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Education (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Job Index (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Market Research and TV: Consumer Expenditures Study (LSCE) #2-4 (Offsite-box 3505, Folder 18-21)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Market Research and TV: Education Series Survey (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 1-2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Market Research and TV: Marketing Laboratory (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Photographic Awards (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Regional Editions (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Tabbed Copies, 1958 April 21 (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: U.S. Steel (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: What's Going On... Newsletter (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Year-End Issue, "Entertainment" (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 11-12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Ads: "Effectiveness is a Fact of Life" (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 10-12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Circulation (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 13-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: "Department Store Executives Take the Stand" (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Department Store Merchandising Kit (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: "Food Primer" (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: "Glue Spot" (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Job Index (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Market Research and TV: Consumer Expenditures Study (LSCE) #5-6 (Offsite-box 3506, Folder 18-19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 1-3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Owens-Corning (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 4-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: "Report about Life" (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: What's Going On... (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 10-13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3540, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Year-End Issue, "The Good Life" (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Ads: "... is a Fact of Life" (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Ads: "To Me, Life is..." (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 4-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Automotive Industry Booklet (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Circulation (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: International Geophysical Year, "New Portrait of Our Planet" Map (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Job Index (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: "Life is Many Things" (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Market Research and TV: Consumer Expenditures Study (LSCE) #7 (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 17-18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Market Research and TV: Marketing Laboratory (Offsite-box 3507, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Market Research and TV: Marketing Laboratory (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 2-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Radio Corporation of America (RCA), 1938, 1960 (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 1)
  1 phonograph record (78 rpm); 7 in. Label on Side 1: "Part 1. SS 022733. RCA Victor Marches On." Label on Side 2: "Part 2. SS 022734. RCA Victor Marches On." Label on container: "R.C.A. Victor March. 5/18/38. Small 78 rpm record."
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Regional Editions (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 8-9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: "Twenty-Five Years of Life" (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 9-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: What's Going On... (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Year-End Issue, "Twenty-Five Years of Life" (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Ads: Inserts (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 14-15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Alamo Result Piece (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Automotive Industry Booklet (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Circulation (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 14-15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Colleges (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: "Fast Close" (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Job Index (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3508, Folder 17-18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: "One on the Aisle" (Offsite-box 3541, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: The Promise and Purpose of Life (Offsite-box 3542, Folder 1-5)
  1 phonograph record (33 1/3 rpm); 12 in. Label on Side A: "The Promise and Purpose of Life. Side A Inaudible Signal. Produced by Life Magazine." Label on Side B: "The Promise and Purpose of Life. Side B Audible Signal. Produced by Life Magazine."
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 1-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Regional Edition (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Volkswagen Result Piece (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: What's Going On... (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Year-End Issue, "Our Splendid Outdoors" (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 10)
  1 phonograph record (33 1/3 rpm); 7 in. On label: "National Food Brokers Association. 'Hey There, Brokers!' narrated by Eddie Lawrence. Souvenir from Life of the National Food Sales Conference. Chicago, 1960."
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Ads: "Advertised in Life" (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Ads: "Great Markets Live in Life" (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Ads: "Great Moments Live in Life" (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Ads: Inserts (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Circulation (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Edit Side of Life Newsletter (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: "Food" Special Issue (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: "Great Moments Live in Life" (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: "Great Moments Live in Life" (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: "It Happens Every Spring" (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Job Index (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Market Research and TV: Input-Output Model (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3509, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 1-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: "The Most Memorable Events of 1962", 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 12-13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: What's Going On... (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Year-End Issue, "The Sea" (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 10-13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3543, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Ads: "Advertised in Life" (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Ads: Inserts (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963-1964: Ads: TDI Posters (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "All About Life" Review (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Automotive Industry Booklet (Offsite-box 3510, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "Changing Seasons" (Offsite-box 3544, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Circulation (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "Control of the Brain" (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Douglas MacArthur (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Drugs (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Job Index (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "The Major News Stories of 1963", 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "The Making of Life" (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 7-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 4-7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: New York Edition (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "New York Extra" (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 9-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Sears (Offsite-box 3545, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Simmons Guidebook (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "Some Thoughts for Mr. A" (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "TV Trends" Presentation (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: What's Going On... (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: World's Fair (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Year-End Issue, "The Movies" (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3511, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Ads: "Advertised in Life" (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 4-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Ads: Inserts (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Ads: "Life-with-Television" (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 9-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Circulation (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: "Cool Babe Who Has It Made" (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 3-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Corporate Campaign (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Editorial, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Job Index (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: "The Major News Stories of 1964", 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3546, Folder 14-15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Market Research and TV: Nowland Reports (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 6-7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 8-12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: "Mighty Mites" (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Project Mercury (Offsite-box 3547, Folder 1-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: "Prospectus for a Changing World" (Offsite-box 3547, Folder 6-7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Russia (Offsite-box 3547, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Simmons Report (Offsite-box 3547, Folder 9)